

const questionsList = [
    {
        samplequestion: 'We ll remain safe inside as long as  they can t cross the ____ filled with  alligators',
        options: [
            'mott',
            'mote',
            'moat',
            'moet'
        ],
        answer: 'moat'
    },
 {
        samplequestion: 'No one will ____ my writing! he angrily typed, unaware that  no one was even reading it.',
        options: [
            'sensor',
            'censor',
            'senser',
            'censure'
        ],
        answer: 'censor'
    },

    {
        samplequestion: 'I can t ____ the thought  of another  day off! said no one ever',
        options: [
            'bear',
            'bare',
            'beer',
            'blair'
        ],
        answer: 'bear'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'After taking the candy from the children, he scurried to add it to his ____.',
        options: [
            'whoard',
            'whored',
            'hoard',
            'horde'
        ],
        answer: 'hoard'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'Open the ____ he scream as the room filled  with smoke.',
        options: [
            'flue',
            'flew',
            'flu',
            'flee'
        ],
        answer: 'flue'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'If I were to ____  you m I would  say to not take the job',
        options: [
            'cancel',
            'council',
            'counsel',
            'carousel'
        ],
        answer: 'counsel'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'the couple hired an ____ to foretell their fortunes of the day they were married',
        options: [
            'augur',
            'ogre',
            'auger',
            'ogger'
        ],
        answer: 'augur'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'The eulogist at the woodworker s funeral knew she could write the right ____ for the deceased ____.',
        options: [
            'wright, rite',
            'rite, wright',
            'right, write',
            'white, write'
        ],
        answer: 'rite, wright'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'in order to judge  how poeple felt, the senator s office hired a firm to take a ____.',
        options: [
            'pole',
            'poal',
            'po',
            'poll'
        ],
        answer: 'poll'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'Don t sit ____ the fence.',
        options: [
            'on',
            'in',
            'under',
            'beside'
        ],
        answer: 'on'
    },


]

export default questionsList;

/* {
        samplequestion: 'No one will ____ my writing! he angrily typed, unaware that  no one was even reading it.',
        options: [
            'sensor',
            'censor',
            'senser',
            'censure'
        ],
        answer: 'censor'
    },

    {
        samplequestion: 'I can t ____ the thought  of another  day off! said no one ever',
        options: [
            'bear',
            'bare',
            'beer',
            'blair'
        ],
        answer: 'bear'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'After taking the candy from the children, he scurried to add it to his ____.',
        options: [
            'whoard',
            'whored',
            'hoard',
            'horde'
        ],
        answer: 'hoard'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'Open the ____ he scream as the room filled  with smoke.',
        options: [
            'flue',
            'flew',
            'flu',
            'flee'
        ],
        answer: 'flue'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'If I were to ____  you m I would  say to not take the job',
        options: [
            'cancel',
            'council',
            'counsel',
            'carousel'
        ],
        answer: 'counsel'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'the couple hired an ____ to foretell their fortunes of the day they were married',
        options: [
            'augur',
            'ogre',
            'auger',
            'ogger'
        ],
        answer: 'augur'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'The eulogist at the woodworker s funeral knew she could write the right ____ for the deceased ____.',
        options: [
            'wright, rite',
            'rite, wright',
            'right, write',
            'white, write'
        ],
        answer: 'rite, wright'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'in order to judge  how poeple felt, the senator s office hired a firm to take a ____.',
        options: [
            'pole',
            'poal',
            'po',
            'poll'
        ],
        answer: 'poll'
    },
    {
        samplequestion: 'Don t sit ____ the fence.',
        options: [
            'on',
            'in',
            'under',
            'beside'
        ],
        answer: 'on'
    },
 */